♪Myriad delusions cut like knives♪
♪Crushing the moon in the ancient well♪
♪Lost in this life,
I never ask about tomorrow♪
♪When love runs deep,
the moonlight fades♪
♪A cursed fate,
a dream severed over lifetimes♪
=Braving the Famine with My Wife=
=Episode 7=
Zhao Laizi, you'll die today!
Don't hurt these two pretty girls.
I'll be enjoying them soon.
Ladies, close your eyes.
Because it's about to get bloody.
Dong, I want to watch.
I find it thrilling.
Don't hurt Dong!
He is a good man.
Don't be scared.
My buddies and I
will be your husbands soon.
You guys are rotten to the core.
Today, I must give you the respect
and dignity you deserve.
I have a sword
that can destroy everything.
Come, my sword!
Have you lost your mind?
What nonsense are you saying?
Today, you'll die!
(I sense a trace of his aura.)
(Affection 80)
(Affection 100)
Keep the fact that Dong is amazing
between the two of us.
Don't tell the other two.
After all, Dong's love is limited.
Well,
that doesn't sound right.
What's wrong with that?
Do you want to share Dong with others?
I...
Just listen to me.
If you hadn't seen it today,
I wouldn't have let you know.
Anyway, just do as I say.
Cuicui!
Xi... Xi Yun.
Dong, Cuicui...
She's dead.
Although we only spent
a short time together,
I could feel
that Cuicui was a really nice person.
Dong, you can
bring the dead back to life, right?
Please save her.
Her heart meridian was shattered
by a palm strike.
I can save other people,
but Cuicui and I share a destined bond.
Only by cultivating this body of mine
to the Golden Immortal stage
can I save Cuicui.
(This body?)
(What does he mean?)
(Does he have another body?)
(What exactly is Dong?)
Dong, she just said "Xi Yun".
Could it be Xi Yun who harmed her?
It's too early to say so.
I just vowed to protect you forever,
and then this tragedy happened.
Anyone who hurts you
will die!
I'll seal Cuicui's soul
inside her body.
(I used primordial spirit power)
(and Destined Divine Maiden sensed it.)
(Luckily, I suppressed it.)
(This body is nowhere
near her match yet.)
I have locked onto an area.
I'll find you soon.
Clean her body.
Alright.
I'll set up a protective array.
Don't leave the place.
I'll go find Xi Yun.
Dong.
If Xi Yun hurt Cuicui,
what would you do?
I'll avenge Cuicui.
What do you want?
I can help Your Majesty
reclaim the throne.
However, there's one small condition.
I want to be your spouse.
Insolent! How dare you!
I'm sure you know what to do.
Do you want to be the Empress
above all others,
or become a wandering ghost?
Forget your vile schemes.
I would rather die than agree.
What do you want?
What was that?
It's the Ecstasy Pill
that'd poison you.
You need one pill
of antidote every month.
Without taking it, you'll suffer a lot.
Remember,
in this world, only I have the antidote.
You...
Your Majesty,
I love that look in your eyes.
♪With a clap of thunder,
you were cast into the mortal realm♪
♪Silk robes replaced by rags♪
♪Immortal bones buried in the dust♪
♪One thought once stirred the seas♪
♪Now, even cold porridge
is a lucky find♪
♪She was cast out of the golden hall♪
♪With only half a tattered decree♪
♪Her eyes still held a blade's edge♪
♪Saying this world
isn't worth a single moment♪
♪You handed her a bowl of coarse tea♪
♪Telling her to taste
life's bitter and sweet♪
♪So the Supreme Immortal
can fall to dust♪
♪So the Empress
can feel her heart turn cold♪
♪You watched the sunset
in a narrow alley with her♪
♪Hearing a child cry out in pain,
yet still laughing, so silly♪
♪So power is no match
for a bowl of warm porridge♪
♪So heaven can't compare
to a lamp in a broken hut♪
♪From strangers to aching hearts♪
♪From cold words to genuine care♪
♪In the humblest corners
of the mortal world♪
♪You met the most precious person♪
♪She said commoners are just numbers♪
♪You took her to see
the fields turned to scars♪
♪And the old man bent by firewood♪
♪A lifetime of bitterness
on his shoulders♪
♪For the first time,
she set aside her crown♪
♪And held an umbrella
for a drenched street vendor♪
♪You can no longer ride the clouds♪
♪But only toss and turn in the night♪
♪Still kneeling at Heaven's Gate
in your dreams♪
♪Only to wake up
with a flatbread she tossed at you♪
♪Saying, forget the gods♪
♪Just catch your breath first♪
♪So the Supreme Immortal
can fall to dust♪
♪So the Empress can turn for someone♪
♪No longer asking
who stands higher or mightier♪
♪Only asking who stands
at your heart's door now♪
♪If Heaven wants you to pass
through the street's rising smoke first♪
♪If the mortal world cannot hold you♪
♪Then carve the memories
into your palm lines♪
♪From laughter to devotion♪
♪From falling to innocence♪
♪If there's a next life, you'll still♪
♪Love a mortal once more
amidst this suffering♪